▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第二轮
莱巴金娜 6-3 6-4 汤森德 · 赛后场上采访
Eight 1000 events this season.
本赛季八站一千分赛
Rybakina is the only player to win
莱巴金娜是唯一一个
the opening match in all eight as she comes
八站首战全胜的人
through a tough encounter closer
而这一场比比分
than the score line suggests beating Taylor
看上去更胶着
Townsend three and four.
六比三 六比四 赢下汤森德
Well, credit to Townsend.
汤森德也值得肯定
She played a great match, played smart,
她打得很好 也很聪明
was just maybe not good enough,
只是可能还差一点
the consistency
差在稳定性上
to play all the those doubles in the single,
她还要兼顾双打
but against Rybakina.
而对手是莱巴金娜
Elena, I think you know,
埃琳娜 你自己清楚
you've played her before.
你以前跟她交过手
The minute you blink your eyes,
你一眨眼
she can be right back into the match.
她就能重新回到比赛里
She's a tough opponent,
她是个难缠的对手
but you handled her well today.
但你今天处理得很好
Yeah, she is really tough opponent.
是啊 她真的很难打
We played before and it
我们以前交过手
was always a battle and today I'm happy
一直是一场硬仗 今天我很高兴
that I was playing well first set
第一盘我打得不错
and then in the second she stepped in it
第二盘她压了上来
was some close points and it went
有几分咬得很紧
my way some net courts maybe line
结果偏向了我 有擦网也有压线
but I'm super happy with the win
但赢下来我非常高兴
playing great tennis made it to the finals up
你最近状态很好 上周在多伦多
in Toronto what's working right now
打进了决赛 现在你的球
with your game it's so important
是什么在起作用
to get an early start in these kind
在这类赛事里早点进入状态
of tournaments hardcourt season heading
很重要 硬地赛季
over to New York what are you happiest
接下来就是纽约了 今天这场
with about the way you played today.
你最满意的是哪一点
Well, today I'm happy with the serve.
今天我最满意的是发球
Definitely it helped me a lot and yeah,
它确实帮了我很多
last week in Toronto was very difficult.
上周在多伦多非常难
A lot of three set matches,
打了很多三盘
but I'm glad I'm managing to to survive
但我很高兴自己扛了下来
and I think we did a great preparation
我觉得我们和团队
with the team and hopefully I can just keep
准备得很好 希望我能一直
on going.
保持下去
Okay, Magdalena Frech in the next round.
好 下一轮是弗雷赫
You've played her a few times.
你们交过几次手
You've won all those matches.
你全都赢了
What are your thoughts on taking
对上弗雷赫
on Magdalena?
你怎么看
Well, another tough opponent,
又是一个难缠的对手
but I feel like for me the most important
但我觉得最重要的是
to focus on myself right now,
现在先专注在自己身上
try to recover as best as possible
尽可能把身体恢复好
and try try to come with a lot of energy,
然后带着满满的能量上场
good serve.
把发球打好
So yeah, hopefully it's going
希望那会是
to be a nice match and thank you
一场好球 也谢谢
so much for coming and supporting today.
今天到场支持的各位
All right, we love watching you.
好 我们都爱看你打球
Best of luck to you, Elena Rybakina,
祝你好运 埃琳娜·莱巴金娜
everybody through to the third round.
各位 她晋级第三轮